[
    {
    "option1": "There is a shop at the left side.",
    "option2": "There is a shop by the left side.",
    "option3": "There is a shop on the left side.",
    "option4": "There is a shop in the left side.",
    "question": "বাঁদিকে একটা দোকান আছে",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "The baby is walking in the grass.",
    "option2": "The baby is walking at the grass.",
    "option3": "The baby is walking down the grass.",
    "option4": "The baby is walking on the grass.",
    "question": "শিশুটি ঘাসের উপর হাঁটছে",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "The baby is playing on the garden.",
    "option2": "The baby is playing in the garden.",
    "option3": "The baby is playing at the garden.",
    "option4": "The baby is playing of the garden.",
    "question": "শিশুটি বাগানে খেলছে",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "He who is in the middle only is in danger.",
    "option2": "He who is at the middle only is in danger.",
    "option3": "He who is on the middle only is on danger.",
    "option4": "He who is in the middle only is at danger.",
    "question": "যে জন আছে মাঝখানে, তারই বিপদ",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "What is there to the end of our path ?",
    "option2": "What is there in the end of our path ?",
    "option3": "What is there at the end of our path ?",
    "option4": "What is there on the end of our path ?",
    "question": "আমাদের পথের শেষে কি আছে ?",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "The story has no drama in the start.",
    "option2": "The story has no drama on the beginning.",
    "option3": "The story has no drama on the start.",
    "option4": "The story has no drama in the beginning.",
    "question": "গল্পের শুরুতে কোন নাটকীয়তা নেই",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "News of that thief is on today’s newspapers.",
    "option2": "News of that thief is at today’s newspapers.",
    "option3": "News of that thief is in today’s newspapers.",
    "option4": "News of that thief is with today’s newspapers.",
    "question": "আজকের খবরের কাগজে সেই চোরের খবর রয়েছে",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Some say, everything is alright in the end.",
    "option2": "Some say, everything is alright at the end.",
    "option3": "Some say, everything is alright to the end.",
    "option4": "Some say, everything is alright after the end.",
    "question": "কেউ কেউ বলে, শেষে সব ঠিক হয়ে যায়",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Deepak's friends play football in the playground.",
    "option2": "Deepak's friends play football at the playground.",
    "option3": "Deepak's friends play football to the playground.",
    "option4": "Deepak's friends play football on the playground.",
    "question": "দীপকের বন্ধুরা খেলার মাঠে ফুটবল খেলে",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Put your hand to the newspaper.",
    "option2": "Put your hand at the newspaper.",
    "option3": "Put your hand on the newspaper.",
    "option4": "Put your hand in the newspaper.",
    "question": "তোমার হাত খবরের কাগজের ওপর রাখো",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "All runners are same in the start line of a race.",
    "option2": "All runners are same on the start line of a race.",
    "option3": "All runners are same to the start line of a race.",
    "option4": "All runners are same behind the start line of a race.",
    "question": "দৌড়ের শুরুর লাইনে সব দৌড়বাজই সমান",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    }
]